const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1. What does RWD stand for in web design?",
    answer: "Responsive Web Design",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "2. What does REPL stand for in programming environments? ",
    answer: "Read-Eval-Print-Loop",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "3. What does CDN stand for in web infrastructure?",
    answer: "Content Delivery Network",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "4. What does AJAX stand for?",
    answer: "Asynchronous JavaScript and XML",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "5. What does SPA stand for in web development?",
    answer: "Single Page Application",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "6. What does JWT stand for in authentication?",
    answer: "JSON Web Token",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "7. What does SSR stand for in web development?",
    answer: "Server Side Rendering",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "8. What does IIFE stand for in JavaScript?",
    answer: "Immediately Invoked Function Expression",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "9.What does ORM stand for in the context of databases?",
    answer: "Object-Relational Mapping",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "10. What does the acronym REST stand for in API design?",
    answer: "Representational State Transfer",
  },
];

export default questions;
